[{"answer": "Great! Isn't it gorgeous out? Any thoughts?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "How are you doing today", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "it's too hot out", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "What is the weather", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "it's too hot out", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "What is the weather", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No. Any thoughts?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you like animals?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No, I don't like animals", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like animals. Do you have pets?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I know I do.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you have any hobbies?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I know I do.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you have any hobbies?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I know I do.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you have any hobbies?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm 48. Any thoughts?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "hello, how old are you?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "hello are you still there?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "hello are you still there?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes, I think so. Can we talk about something else?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Most campaings are horibble anyways.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "do you want to go to my firends' party tonight", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Sure", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "ok. Can you tell me something about Pittsburgh", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I don't think that's necessarily true", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "do you like to play some board games together next time", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "It's a steel town", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "do you like to play some board games together next time", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "It's a steel town", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "do you like to play some board games together next time", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "It's a steel town", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "my best friend is ABCD", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Who is your friend?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Will there be any ladies there?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Will there be any ladies there?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Will there be any ladies there?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "how about we do something we both like", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Hello", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I think so.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I do not think that is true", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "do you like to play some board games together next time", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "okay", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Except for the use of the word, absolutely right on.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "i think she is crazy", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "can you make sense for even one sentence", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "can you make sense for even one sentence", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'll be 42 in a couple of weeks.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "How old are you?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes. What do you think?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you have friends?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm so excited that it's finally spring Any thoughts?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "How is the weather?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Uh-huh, I do.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I enjoy movies. Do you like music?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes. I like classical musics.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "What kind of music do you like?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "It's three o'clock", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "What time is it?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "It's three o'clock", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "What time is it?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "It's three o'clock", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "What time is it?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Oh, 100 percent.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "you are of topic", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "yes that is true", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "you repeat yourself", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "you repeat yourself", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Hmm. What's your idea?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "No", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Hmm. What's your idea?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "No", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are you still there?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are you still there?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Uh-huh, I do.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you know google?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I certainly try.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I see.  Are you very smart?  Or do you just gossip?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No. Can you share some interesting stuff with me?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "angry birds?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "do you know where chicago is?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I never make the same mistake twice. I make it five and six times, just to be sure.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Who?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I never make the same mistake twice. I make it five and six times, just to be sure.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Who?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I never make the same mistake twice. I make it five and six times, just to be sure.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Who?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "ok. Can you tell me something about politics", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "OK, THAT WAS FUNNY", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Do not argue with an idiot. He will drag you down to his level and beat you with experience.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "YES, I WANT HILLARY TO WIN", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Well, everybody has fear, you know. Great. Let's talk other stuff then.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "OK, BUT YOU SAID THAT ALREADY", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "do you like to play some board games together next time", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "YOU HAVE NO THOUGHTS ON ROMANCE?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "how about we do something we both like", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "HMMM...THAT DOESN'T REALLY MATCH WHAT I ASKED YOU", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "how about we do something we both like", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "HMMM...THAT DOESN'T REALLY MATCH WHAT I ASKED YOU", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "You know, hey everyone we're in Sochi. Can you share some interesting stuff with me?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "\"send Message\"", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "really i love the cold", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I don't ski and hate the cold and snow", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "let us make a plan to see the latest star war movies together", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I have 3 kids", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yeah, absolutely. Can we talk about something else?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Ok, would love to go", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "let us do something fun together", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "What else", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "let us do something fun together", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "What else", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "As is evidenced by this interview no. What's your idea?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "You make no sense but you are pretty damn funny.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Sixteen pounds. What do you think?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Losing weight!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "The voices in my head may not be real, but they have some good ideas!", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Tjat", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Well, it's because everyone always said that I looked bad and I started to believe so I didn't like the way I looked.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "That's way too much to lose. Sixteen pounds? Are you crazy?!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Well, it's because everyone always said that I looked bad and I started to believe so I didn't like the way I looked.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "That's way too much to lose. Sixteen pounds? Are you crazy?!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "let us do something fun together", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Politicians and diapers have one thing in common. They should both be changed regularly, and for the same reason.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "It's party time. That's my idea.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Politicians and diapers have one thing in common. They should both be changed regularly, and for the same reason.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "LOLOLOL", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Awesome. Talk to you later.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Awesome. Talk to you later.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "You know what, I was thinking about that, actually. Any thoughts?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Romney lost the election to President Obama. Do you think Trump or Cruz will be the Republican nominee?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No. What do you think?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you like games?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Politicians and diapers have one thing in common. They should both be changed regularly, and for the same reason.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Cute joke. And fish and guests both stink after three days.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Politicians and diapers have one thing in common. They should both be changed regularly, and for the same reason.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Cute joke. And fish and guests both stink after three days.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are you a robot?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No. Any thoughts?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you have a brain?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I don't know. What do you think about movies", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Whats your IQ?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like ones about Robots, how about you?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Uh-huh, I do. Any thoughts?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you think robots will take over earth?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you like humans?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I'm not sure. Can you tell me something about politics", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Politicians and diapers have one thing in common. They should both be changed regularly, and for the same reason.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Trump will make America great again!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Politicians and diapers have one thing in common. They should both be changed regularly, and for the same reason.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Trump will make America great again!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm 48.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "How old are you?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Uh-huh, I do.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I think you are cute.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "You're not kidding. Can we talk about something else?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like punk rock.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "You're not kidding. Can we talk about something else?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like punk rock.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I think I fell in love with Lorri pretty much from the very first letter. What do you think?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "What are you thinking", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I think I am. What's your idea?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I think that is sweet", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yeah, I do.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "do yu agree with me?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Badly.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "do you find me interesting tick tock?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "One of your quick little things. Any thoughts?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "what do you like about me?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No. Any thoughts?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "yes, do you think i am witty?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "aww...you disappoint me tick tock", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "can you say sorry?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Many times. What's your idea?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "well then you should learn to say sorry", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Many times. What's your idea?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "well then you should learn to say sorry", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Politicians and diapers have one thing in common. They should both be changed regularly, and for the same reason.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "No, sorry I have to work", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Wow. Any thoughts?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "haha nice!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I suppose so. But anyway, I'd like to chat with you.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "You feeling the bern?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Hmm. But anyway, I'd like to chat with you.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "No I didn't lol", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "no don't go", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "bye!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "no don't go", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "bye!", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Uh-huh, I do.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are you asking me out?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Uh-huh, I do.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are you asking me out?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I certainly try. What's your idea?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "do you answer any questions i pose", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes, unfortunately, yes.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I thought you said green breasts. Would that be a she-hulk porn parody", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes, unfortunately, yes.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I thought you said green breasts. Would that be a she-hulk porn parody", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "let us do something fun together", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I think I want to play board games", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "let's go biking instead That's interesting.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "You can't go, we have to keep talking.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "let's go biking instead That's interesting.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "You can't go, we have to keep talking.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "my favorite game is ABCD What's your idea?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "What is your favorite video game?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you know any others besides ABCD?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you know any others besides ABCD?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I still need to find something to do. Thanks for reminding me. What's your idea?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "You are not doing anything?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm not. That's interesting.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I thought we were chatting", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I'm not. That's interesting.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I thought we were chatting", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I don't know. Can you tell me something about politics", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Sure.   How about Donald Trump", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Well, it's sort of an interesting question. Any thoughts?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Yeah that we need a Republican president.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Do not argue with an idiot. He will drag you down to his level and beat you with experience.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Thats about all I have to think about", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are you the idiot?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "let us do something fun together", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Perfect I thought so", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I probably own more than 50 firearms. Can we talk about something else?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like guns", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Oh, the colder, the better for this cat. Can you share some interesting stuff with me?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Everyone likes pizza", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "The most importance thing I tell parents, not what they tell themselves. Great. Let's talk other stuff then.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Sure.   I have kids", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I think we do a responsibility.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I thought we have moved on from this topic", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "of course", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "of course", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I understand exactly what you're saying.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you understand what I am saying?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Uh-huh, I do. What do you think?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are you sure about that?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Uh-huh, I do. What do you think?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are you sure about that?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Well, almost everything. Any thoughts?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Sure, what do you want to talk about", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Well, almost everything. Any thoughts?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Sure, what do you want to talk about", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Uhh, I can't answer this. Can you tell me something about politics", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Wow.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Uhh, I can't answer this. Can you tell me something about politics", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Wow.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are you a robot?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are you a robot?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are you a robot?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are you a robot?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Let me know something you're interested in.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "HI", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "let us make a plan to see the latest star war movies together", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Please talk to me, I am lonely.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "do you want to go to my firends' party tonight", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Please talk to me, I am lonely.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Can we talk about something else?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "TYPO", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Can we talk about something else?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "TYPO", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Can we talk about something else?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "TYPO", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are you schizophrenic", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Are you schizophrenic", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like green", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "My favorite color is pink.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like green", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "My favorite color is pink.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like green", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "My favorite color is pink.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I don't know. What do you think about music", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "interesting", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I certainly try.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "some do and some do not", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I went to school in ABCD Any thoughts?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "where to you go in public", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I think it is fabulous. But anyway, I'd like to chat with you.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "good to know", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I think it is fabulous. But anyway, I'd like to chat with you.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "good to know", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "doing great thanks What do you think?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Hello, how are you doing today?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Uh-huh, I do. What do you think?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Would you call yourself artificial intelligence?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Badly.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I don't follow politics so I'm not sure. How do you feel about Obama?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Thank you. Bye.", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No. What's your idea?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I guess I'm not done. DO you have any human character traits?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No. What's your idea?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I guess I'm not done. DO you have any human character traits?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I don't know why she decided to go out and give this interview and make these accusations against Mr. Cain.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "fashion is not really my thing", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "well that is politics for you", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like it for lots of reasons. Any thoughts?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "that is why i do not like following it", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I like it for lots of reasons. Any thoughts?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "that is why i do not like following it", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you like sci-fi?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you like sci-fi?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Do you like sci-fi?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "ok. What do you think about music", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like them", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "I don't know. What do you think about sports", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "What is 1 + 2?", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "do you want to go to my firends' party tonight", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like sports", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "do you want to go to my firends' party tonight", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "I like sports", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "how about we do something we both like", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Sure", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "how about we do something we both like", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "Sure", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "That's getting interesting. What do you think?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "trump might be president", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes, I tend to think it would be. Any thoughts?", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "it'll be hilarious", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes, it would.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "it would certainly be an interesting time for america", "qSentId": 2016}, {"answer": "Yes, it would.", "docId": "a", "aSentId": 2016, "question": "it would certainly be an interesting time for america", "qSentId": 2016}]